《铁血战士》
你看来很精神 达奇
You're looking good, Dutch.
很久不见了 将军
It's been a long time, General.
进去里面谈吧
Come on inside.
18小时前
Eighteen hours ago,
我们在这小国失去一架直升机
we lost a chopper carrying a cabinet minister
上面载着内阁成员及其助理
and his aide from this charming little country.
收到的讯号显示 他们的位置大约在这里
We've got a transponder fix on their position about here.
这位内阁成员...
This cabinet minister...
喜欢乱窜吗
does he always travel on the wrong side of the border?
是直升机偏离原定航道
Apparently they strayed off course...
他们肯定落入了游击队手中
and we're fairly certain they're in guerrilla hands.
为什么不用正规部队去营救他们
Why don't you use the regular army?
而要用我们这些特种部队
What do you need us for?
因为有笨蛋认为你们是最好的 指定要你们
'Cause some damned fool accused you of being the best.
狄龙! 你这贱人...
Dillon! You son of a bitch!
怎么了?
What's the matter?
CIA让你坐太久办公室吗?
The CIA got you pushing too many pencils?
够了吗?
Had enough?
你可以放轻松些的
Make it easy on yourself, Dutch.
好吧...好吧...好吧!
OK! OK, OK.
你永远不知什么时候该停
You never knew when to quit.
真高兴又见到你!
Damn good to see you.
你这条领带算是什么?
What's this fucking tie business?
算了 别谈我的领带啦
Come on. Forget about my tie.
我听说你在柏林的那次任务
I heard about that job you pulled in Berlin.
完美漂亮 达奇
Very nice, Dutch.
就像美好的旧时光
Good old days.
是啊 美好的旧时光
Yeah, I like the good old days.
为什么你不参加利比亚的那次行动?
Then how come you passed on Libya?
轰炸不是我喜欢的作战方式
That wasn't my style.
你可没有特定的作战方式
You got no style. You know that.
别这样告诉我
Come on.
你为什么不肯参加呢?
Why did you pass?
我们是拯救小组...
We're a rescue team...
而不是暗杀小组
not assassins.
我们这次的任务是什么?
Now, what do we got to do?
这位内阁成员
The cabinet minister's important
对我们在这地区很重要
to our scope of operations in this part of the world.
达奇 将军的意思是说...
The general's saying a couple of our friends are about to get squeezed.
我们不能让他们被害
We can't let that happen.
我们需要最好的小组
We need the best.
这就是你的小组在此的原因
That's why you're here.
继续说
Go on.
很简单的行动 一天就能搞定
Simple setup. One- day operation.
我们到直升机那里寻找游击队的足迹
We pick up their trail at the chopper, grab those hostages,
救出人质 在他们发现之前
and bounce back, and cross the border...
我们已经越过边境回来
before anybody knows we were there.
"我们"是什么意思
What do you mean, "we"?
我跟你们一起行动
I'm going in with you, Dutch.
将军 你知道我的队伍一向是单独行动的
General, my team always works alone. You know that.
抱歉 少校 我们各有各的命令
We all have our orders, Major.
一旦完成任务后
Once you reach your objective...
狄龙将接管这次行动
Dillon will evaluate the situation and take charge.
目的地已标在地图上 无线电频道也已调好
Rendezvous points and radio freqs are indicated and fixed.
每四小时跟指挥部联络一次
AWACs contact on four- hour intervals.
谁是我们的支援?
Who's our backup?
没有支援 老朋友
No such thing, ol' buddy.
这是单程任务
This is a one- way ticket.
我们越过边界 一切就只能靠自己
Once we cross that border, we're on our own.
这任务越听越有趣
This is getting better by the minute.
比利! 有天我去我女朋友那里...
Hey, Billy. The other day, I went up to my girlfriend.
我对她说 "我想跟你做爱"
I said, l'd like a little pussy.
她说 "我也是 我的跟房子一样大"
She said, "Me, too. Mine's as big as a house!"
知道吗 她希望性器小 因为她的...
See, she wanted a littler one 'cause hers was...
跟房子一样大...
big as a house.
把那恶心的烟草拿远一点
Get that stinking shit out of my face, will ya?
都是愚蠢的无能弱者
Bunch of slack- jawed faggots around here!
烟草可令你跟我一样
This stuff will make you a damn sexual tyrannosaurus
成性超人
just like me.
塞到屁眼里去吧 布雷
Yeah? Strap this on your sore ass, Blain.
这打火机是72年在北越
That was in '72.
我跟达奇各得一个作奖励
Me and Dutch both got one.
嚼烟草真的是个很恶心的习惯
That's a real nasty habit you got there.
到了
Right.
你知道我多怀念跟你一起战斗
Never knew how much I missed this, Dutch.
你啥时有这么聪明了
You never were that smart.
霍金斯 去吧!
Hawkins, you're up.
准备好了
Lines away.
直升机是头部中弹的
The pilots have each got one round in the head.
他们抢走了里面所有东西
Whoever hit it, stripped the shit out of it.
游击队是用热导弹把它击落
Took him out with a heat- seeker.
还有 少校
Something else, Major.
什么事?
Ehn?
这不是一架普通的直升机
This is no ordinary army taxi.
在我看来更像侦查机
It looks more like a surveillance bird to me.
找到他们留下的足迹了吗?
Pick up the trail yet?
比利正在找
Billy's on it.
狄龙 这事越来越复杂
Heat- seeker, Dillon.
游击队怎么会有热导弹
That's pretty sophisticated for half- assed mountain boys.
少校
Major
我想他们的装备越来越好了
I guess they're getting better equipped every day.
原来有12个人
There were 12 guerrillas.
游击队把他们从直升机捉走
They took the two men from the helicopter...
但是 还有别的足迹...
but there's something else.
什么意思?
What?
有六个穿美国陆军军鞋的人
Six men wearing US- issued army boots.
他们是从北方来的
They came in from the north
他们一路追踪那些游击队
and then they followed the guerrillas.
这事你知道吗?
Mean anything to you?
可能只是另一组游击队罢了
Probably just another rebel patrol.
他们经常在这一带出没
They operate in here all the time.
- 你去看看能发现些什么 - 是 长官
- See what you can find. - Yes, sir.
比利找到什么?
What's he got?
跟以前的一样
Same business.
游击队捉走了两个人
Guerrillas hauling two guys in the chopper...
被一些穿美军装备的人追踪
followed by men with American equipment.
还记得上次在阿富汗吗?
Do you remember Afghanistan?
尝试把它忘记吧! 来
Trying to forget it. Come on. Let's go.
圣母玛丽亚...
Holy mother of God.
吉米·霍普
"Jim Hopper."
麦克 将他们放下来
Mac, cut them down.
我认得他是北卡州部队的
I knew these men. Green Berets out of Fort Bragg.
他们来这里做什么?
What the hell were they doing here?
我不知道 达奇
I don't know, Dutch.
这太不人道了!
This is inhuman.
没有人告诉我这区域有活动
Nobody told me there was an operation in this area.
他们不应该在这里
They shouldn't have been here.
是有人派他们来的
Well, somebody sent them.
游击队把他们剥皮?
The guerrillas skinned them?
他们为什么要这样做?
Why did they skin them?
军人不应是这样死法的
Ain't no way for no soldier to die.
比利 到底发生什么事?
What happened here, Billy?
很奇怪 少校
Strange, Major.
这里曾经发生枪战
There was a fire fight.
他们向四面八方盲目射击
They were shooting in all directions.
我无法想像吉米会走进埋伏
Can't believe Jim Hopper walked into an ambush.
我不相信他中了埋伏
I don't believe he did.
我找不到半点痕迹
I can't find a single track.
完全没有道理
Just doesn't make sense.
霍普其他的队员呢?
What about the rest of Hopper's men?
没有他们的踪迹
There's no sign, sir.
他们根本没有离开这里
They never left here.
他们就像突然消失了一样
Hell, it's like they just disappeared.
继续追踪游击队的足迹 我们去救人质
Stick with the guerrilla trail. Let's get the hostages.
出发吧
We move,
每个人隔5公尺 不要作声!
five- meter spread. No sound.
是时候把武器拿出来了
It's time to let Old Painless out of the bag.
血债血偿的时间
Payback time.
你这讨厌的家伙在做什么?
You're ghostin' us, mother fucker.
我不管你有多重要
I don't care who you are back in the world.
如果你再不小心暴露行踪
You give our position one more time...
我会神不知鬼不觉的让你流血
I'll bleed you real quiet
让你留下来等死
and leave you here.
你听清楚了吗?
Got that?
他们杀了一个人质!
He killed one of the hostages.
我们准备进攻
We move.
麦克和布雷对付机枪堡
Mac, Blain...the nest.
比利和宾对付警卫
Billy, Poncho...the guard.
霍金斯和狄龙作支援
Hawkins, Dillon...backup.
一切布署好后 我便攻击他们的燃料库
Once they're set, I hit the fuel dump.
解决了一个
One down.
他在做什么?
What the hell's he doing?
搞什么?
What the fuck?
表演时间到
Show time, kid.
目标是中央那房屋
Target's the center, on the upper level!
小心九点方向!
Dutch, on your nine!
解决那个!
Get that mother!
钉在此处吧
Stick around.
人质在里面
Hostages are inside!
你好吗?
Knock knock.
我去追截他们
I got 'em !
霍金斯 通知指挥部我们现在的位置及状况
Hawkins, call in position and situation.
用无线电跟指挥部联络
Get Connor for the hook!
知道 少校!
You got it, Major.
该死
Shit.
麦克
Mac,
找到其他的人质吗?
any sign of the other hostage?
找到另外一个 也已经死了
Found the other guy. He's dead, too...
还找到从直升机拆下的齿轮
and the kid from the chopper.
如果他们是中美洲人 那我就是中国人了
But if they're Central American, l'm a Goddamn Chinaman.
这样说那阁员应是CIA
From the looks of it, our cabinet minister was CIA.
还有 我们运气不错
Another thing, Major. We were lucky.
除了游击队外 还有苏联军事顾问
Other guys we waxed...Russian military advisers.
看来有大规模军事计划进行
Something pretty big was gonna happen here.
做得好 麦克
Good work, Mac.
清理一下现场 不要留下蛛丝马迹
Clear the area. No traces.
叫大家准备离去
Get the men ready to move.
好的
Right.
那杂种待在那里死也不走开
Son of a bitch is dug in like an Alabama tick.
你中了弹 在流血!
You're hit. You're bleeding, man.
我没时间流血
I ain't got time to bleed.
好吧
Oh...OK.
有时间躲一躲吗?
You got time to duck?
真他妈漂亮!
This is goddamn beautiful.
中正头奖!
Goddamn jackpot.
比想像中更多机密!
This is more than we ever thought we'd get.
给我们一网打尽
Now we got those bastards.
捉个正着
We got 'em.
我想这才是你要找的东西
I think this is what you're looking for.
你利用我们!
You set us up!
你告诉我的都是废话 你骗我们!
It's all bullshit! All of it.
什么内阁成员等等...
The cabinet minister, the whole business.
骗我们来这里替你卖命
Got us in here to do your dirty work.
我们刚阻止一次大型入侵
We just stopped a major invasion.
他们本来三天内便会侵略
In three days, they'd have crossed the border with the stuff.
为什么挑我们?
Why us?
没其他人能完成这任务
Because nobody else could've pulled it off.
骗你是因为不这样的话你不会来
You're pissed about the cover story? I needed it to get you in here.
那你告诉霍普什么样的故事
What story did you hand Hopper?
我们花了几个月才找到这里
Look, we've been looking for this place for months.
那架直升机被击中时 我的手下在里面
My men were in that chopper when it got hit!
霍普是要来拯救我的手下
Hopper was supposed to get them.
而他却不见了
He disappeared.
他没有失踪 他是被活活的剥了皮
He didn't disappear. He was skinned alive!
而我的命令就是 送能消灭凶手的人到这里
My orders were to get somebody to crack these bastards!
所以你编故事骗我们来送死
So you cooked up a story and dropped us in a meat grinder.
你是怎么了 狄龙?
What happened to you, Dillon?
你以前是个值得信赖的人啊!
You used to be somebody I could trust.
我清醒了
I woke up.
你为什么不能醒过来?
Why don't you?
你是项资产...
You're an asset...
一项可以牺牲的资产
an expendable asset...
我用你来完成任务
and I used you to get the job done.
明白吗?
Got it?
我的手下不是可以随便牺牲的!
My men are not expendable.
我也不做这种事!
And I don't do this kind of work.
少校! 少校!
Major! Major!
我们有麻烦!
We stepped into some real shit here.
空中侦查说到处都是游击队
Air surveillance says we got guerillas all over the place.
就在一两公里范围内
Can't be more than one, two miles away.
他们大概多久会到?
How much time?
半个小时内
Half hour, maybe less.
告诉麦克 五分钟后出发
Tell Mac we move in five.
等一等 她跟我们一起走
Wait. She goes with us.
她非常有价值
She's too valuable.
她一定知道整个部署
She's got the whole of that work.
她一有机会便会泄露我们行踪
She'll give away our position any chance she gets.
不行!
No deal.
少校 你必须听我命令
You're still under orders, Major.
你下命令还是由我来?
You wanna make that call or should I?
你自己负责看着她
She's your baggage.
你跟不上的话 便自理
You fall behind, and you're on your own.
直升机在这里升降太危险
Place is too hot for a pickup.
他们不会在这里接我们 除非我们越过边境
They won't touch us till we get over the border.
比利! 哪条路可以离开这里
Hey, Billy, give me a way out of this hole.
空中侦查说我们被包围
Aerial says we're cut off.
唯一的出路是那山谷 它会把我们引向东边
The only way out is that valley that leads east...
那条路非常险峻
but I wouldn't wish that on a broke- dick dog.
我们没得选择
Not much choice.
宾 你开路 尽快前进!
Poncho, take lead. Double- time it.
放开我
还有很长的路要走
你给我乖一点
狄龙
Dillon!
狄龙 过来
Dillon! Over here.
转身
Turn around.
为什么?
Why?
谢谢!
Thanks.
好说!
Anytime.
比利!
Billy! Billy!
有天我对女朋友说
The other day, I was going down on my girlfriend...
你的性器很大
and I said to her"Jeez, you got a big pussy.
你的性器很大...
Jeez, you got a big pussy."
她问为什么要说两次
She said, "Why did you say that twice?"
我说我没有说两次啊!
And I said, "l didn't."
明白吗? 因为洞太大 有回音...
See, it was because of the echo. It was...
这里 这里...
Over here. Over here. Over here.
转身 转身
Turn around. Turn around.
转身 转身 这里
Turn around. Turn around. Over here.
好说
Anytime.
他妈的!
Goddamn. Whew.
老兄
Buddy, buddy, buddy.
我以前也去过可怕的丛林 但都比不上这里
I've seen some bad- ass bush before, but nothing like this.
同意 这地方真是怪异
I hear you. This shit's something.
柬埔寨和这比 都成天堂了
Makes Cambodia look like Kansas.
喝点这个吧
Que pasa, amigo?
有点家的味道!
A little taste off home.
在这种地方失去自我控制 就麻烦了
You lose it here, you're in a world of hurt.
不要拖延我们 起来
Come on, sweetheart. Stop sandbaggin' it. Now get up.
快起来!
Come on, get up.
你起不起来?
Would you get up?
不用浪费力气了
Ni lo intentes.
也许你应用皮带牵着她走
Maybe you better put her on a leash, agent man.
你有胆再一试!
Try it again...please.
别动!
Callate.
比利为什么这样紧张害怕?
What's got Billy so spooked?
我也不知道 少校
Can't say, Major.
一早就这样了
Been acting squirrelly all morning.
他那鼻子是很奇怪的
That damn nose of his...it's weird.
是什么 比利?
What is it? Billy.
你没问题吧?
What the hell is wrong with you?
那树上有些东西
There's something in those trees.
你看到上面有什么?
Do you see anything? Up there ahead.
什么也看不到
Nothing.
你认为是什么?
What do you think?
我想可能没什么吧 少校
I guess it's nothing, Major.
好了! 别再挣扎了
Please! Please!
比利 搜查左边!
Billy, break back.
麦克 右边!
Back right.
这是...
What the...
这不是她的血
This isn't her blood.
你将他怎样了!
What the hell did you do to him?
少校 你最好来看一看!
Major, you better take a look at this.
你找到霍金斯了吗?
Did you find Hawkins?
我...我也不知道
I...I can't tell.
老天爷!
What in God's name?
我想那是霍金斯的血
I think it's Hawkins.
那他的尸体呢?
Where the hell is his body?
不知所踪
There's no sign of it.
问她到底发生什么事
Ask her what happened.
究竟发生什么事?
你到底看到什么?
他在哪里?
我什么也没看到
- 快说 - 我没看到他去了哪里
他在哪里 快说
什么?
她说这丛林活过来抓走了他
She says the jungle...it just came alive and took him.
放屁! 她不是这样说的
Bullshit! That's not what she said!
她说的完全没有道理
What she said doesn't make any sense.
游击队一直在追我们
Those sappers followed us...
乱说 他们在我们前面
Hell, they've been ahead of us!
这女人想赶到前面
This woman's been running us right to 'em !
别吵了
Hold it!
好了!
他们怎么没拿走他的 无线电或是武器?
Why didn't they take his radio or his weapon?
她为什么没逃走?
Why didn't she escape?
霍普!
Hopper.
什么?
What?
他们像对付霍普一样对霍金斯
They did the same thing to Jim Hopper.
搜寻霍金斯的尸体
I want Hawkins' body found.
扫荡搜索队形!
Sweep pattern.
往我们来的方向搜索 检查这50公尺的范围
Double back. 50 meters.
开始行动
Let's go.
出来吧 你们这些杂种
Come on in, you fuckers.
出来吧
Come on in.
我的武器在等待你们
Old Painless is waiting.
接触敌人!
Sergeant!
出来吧 王八蛋!
Mother fucker! Fucker!
狗娘养的! 你这杂种
Mother fucker! You mother fucker!
发生什么事?
What happened?
我看到它
I saw it.
你看到什么?
You saw what?
我看到它
I saw it.
布雷 身上没有火药痕迹
Blain. No powder burns,
没有碎片
no shrapnel.
他的伤口是烧焦的
The wound's all fused, cauterized.
什么东西会造成这样的伤口
What the hell could have done this to a man?
麦克! 麦克 看着我!
Mac. Mac, look at me!
是谁做的?
Who did this?
我一点也不知道
I don't know, goddamn it.
我看到一些...一些东西
I saw s- something.
什么也找不到
Not a thing,
一点痕迹也没有
not a fucking trace.
没有血迹...没有尸体
No blood, no bodies.
我们什么也没打到!
We hit nothing.
狄龙 你最好快跟总部联络
Dillon...better get on the radio.
麦克!
Mac.
士官!
Sergeant!
是 长官
Yes, sir.
在山脊上布置个防御阵地
I want a defensive position above that ridge...
把所有爆炸品都准备好
mined with everything we've got.
把他放好 我们带他一起走
Put him in his poncho. Take him with us.
我来办!
I got him.
走吧!
Vamonos.
少校 我已经装设好照明弹 手榴弹及地雷
Major...I set up flares, frags, and CIAymores.
没有什么能不碰到这些东西 进到这阵地来
Nothing's coming near this place without tripping on something.
谢谢你 士官
Thank you, sergeant.
麦克
Mac.
他是个好军人
He was a good soldier.
他是...我的朋友
He was, um...my friend.
再见了 我的兄弟!
Good- bye, bro.
火焰一号 我重复
Blazer one, I repeat,
必须把我们撤离
extraction necessary.
再说一遍 火焰一号
Say again, Blazer one.
再说一遍
Say again.
你的要求不被接受
Request for extraction denied.
你的位置仍旧暴露在敌人的火力网下
Area is still compromised.
请前进到3000位置 我们在那里接你们
Proceed to sector 3,000 for prisoner extraction. Priority, out.
下次联络时间是9:30
Next contact 0930.
知道了 火焰一号
Roger, Blazer one.
10:30联络
10:30 hours.
贱人
Damn bastards.
他们说我们的位置还太远
They say we're still in too far,
他们不能冒险前来接我们
and they can't risk coming in.
我们是资产 狄龙
We're assets, Dillon.
可以牺牲的资产!
Expendable assets.
CIA就是这样
It comes with the job.
这点我可以接受
I can accept it.
胡说 你跟我们一样生气
Bullshit. You're just like the rest of us.
直升机不会来这里就是了
Shitload of good a chopper's gonna do us in here anyhow.
士官
Sergeant?
士官! 士官!
Sergeant! Sergeant!
今天谁攻击我们?
Who hit us today?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只看到一个有伪装的东西
I only saw one of them camouflaged.
他在那里
He was there.
那对眼睛...忽然消失了
Those eyes disappeared.
你说什么?
What was that?
那对眼睛 他们...他们消失不见了
Those eyes, they...they disappeared.
我只知道一件事 少校
I know one thing, Major.
我对准向它射击
I drew down and fired straight at it.
我射了200轮以上
Capped off 200 rounds in the minigun...
我把所有子弹射光了
Full pack.
但是一点用处也没有
Nothing...
这世上没有什么东西 在那个范围内
nothing on this earth could have lived.
还能生存的
Not at that range.
麦克 你站第一班 然后去休息一会
Mac, you take first watch then you get some rest, OK?
问她看到什么? 问她霍金斯怎么了?
Ask her what she saw. Ask her what happened to Hawkins.
问她吧!
Go ahead, ask her.
你看到什么了
丛林活过来把他抓走
还是那句话
Same fucking thing.
丛林活过来把他抓走
The jungle, it came alive and took him.
比利 你一定知道些什么 到底是什么?
Billy, you know something. What is it?
我感到害怕
I'm scared, Poncho.
放屁! 你不怕任何人的
Bullshit. You ain't afraid of no man.
外面有东西在等我们
There's something out there waiting for us...
而且并不是人
and it ain't no man.
我们全都会死
We're all gonna die.
这家伙已经失去理智
The man's losing it. He's losing his cool.
只不过是有些敌人在附近
Nothing but a couple guys running around...
我们可以应付
and we gotta take 'em.
你还是不明白 狄龙
Still don't understand, Dillon, do you?
不管那是什么
Whatever it is out there,
它杀了霍普
it killed Hopper...
现在它要杀死我们
and now it wants us.
我们又在一起了
Here we are again, bro...
只有你和我
just you and me.
一样的月亮 一样的丛林
Same kind of moon, same kind of jungle.
那晚我们喝酒来壮胆
Real number- ten night,
你还记得吗?
remember?
整个部队
Whole platoon...
32个人都被剁成肉酱
32 men chopped into meat...
除了你和我
and we walk out, just you and me.
再没有别人
Nobody else.
我们是最好的战士
Right on top of them.
这根本不算一回事
Not a scratch. Not a fucking scratch.
你知道不管是谁把你杀死
You know, whoever got you...
他会回来找我们
he'll come back again,
只要他敢回来
and when he does...
我会把你的名字刻在他身上
I'm going to cut your name into him.
什么事?
What the hell is it?
麦克!
Mac!
这边!
This way!
- 你在那里 麦克? - 在这边
- Where are you? - Over here!
你在那里?
Where are you?
麦克!
Mac!
麦克! 该死!
Mac! Fuck!
麦克 你在哪?
Mac, where are you?
老天!
Jesus.
捉逮到你了 贱人
I got you, mother fucker.
我杀死你
I killed you, you fuck.
老天 你杀了一只猪
Jesus, you killed a pig.
你是不是应该找只大点的?
Think you could have found something bigger?
是啊 去你妈的!
Fuck you, Poncho. Fuck you.
那女人在那里?
Where's the girl?
他妈的!
Aw, shit!
为什么没人看着她?
Why the hell wasn't anybody watching her?
她为什么没有逃走?
Why didn't she try to get away?
你看她 她吓坏了!
Look at her. She's scared out of her mind.
少校 你最好来看看
Major, you better take a look at this.
布雷的尸体不见了
Blain's body, it's gone.
它避过了我们设下的陷阱
It came in through the tripwires.
在我们面前把布雷带走
Took it right out from under our noses.
是那只猪误触陷阱
That boar had to set off a tripflare...
再没有其它足印
because there ain't no other tracks.
怎么有人能通过陷阱
How could anyone get through this...
带走布雷又不让我们发觉?
and carry out Blain without us knowing it?
我是指他为什么没杀人呢?
Why didn't he try and kill one of us?
他来只是拿那尸体
He came to get the body.
他一次只杀一个
He's killing us one at a time.
就像猎人一样
Like a hunter.
他是利用这些树潜进来的
He's using the trees.
昨天你看到什么?
Yesterday, what did you see?
你在浪费你的时间
You're wasting your time.
别再跟我们玩把戏
No more games.
我不知道它是什么
I don't know what it was. It...
继续
Go on.
它会变颜色
It changed colors
就像变色龙一样
like the chameleon.
它利用这丛林
It uses the jungle.
你说他们是被蜥蜴杀死的?
Blain and Hawkins were killed by a lizard?
发什么神经
That's a bullshit psych job.
外面最多只有两三人在活动
There's 2 or 3 men out there.
去他妈的蜥蜴
Fucking lizard!
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
安娜
Anna.
Anna,
这东西在追捕我们
the thing is hunting us.
所有的人
All of us.
你明白吗?
You know that.
你以为你在做什么?
What the hell are you doing?
我们需要这里的每个人
We'll need everyone.
我要带她回去
l'm taking her back.
我们五分钟后就要走
We leave in five minutes.
我们还不能走
We're not going yet.
听着 救援部队很快便到
Rendezvous is ten miles away.
你以为直升机会等我们吗?
You think the chopper's going to wait?
狄龙 我们必须共同抵抗敌人
We make a stand now,
否则谁都不能活着出去
or nobody will be left.
还有一件事
There is something else.
那个大个子被杀的时候
When the big man was killed,
你一定弄伤了它
you must have wounded it.
它的血滴在树叶上
Its blood was on the leaves.
如果它会流血 那么我们就能杀掉它
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
小心
Look out.
你认为这童子军玩意有效?
You really think this Boy Scout bullshit's gonna work?
它能看到那些金属线
It can see tripwires.
但可能看不到这陷阱
Maybe it can't see this.
少废话了 赶紧帮忙
Instead of complaining, maybe you should help.
怎么你认为它一定会走这里
What makes you think he'll come through here?
50码半径内的每棵树上 都绑上了金属线
The trees have tripwires every 50 yards.
这是剩下的唯一通路
This is the only way in.
当我还是小孩子时
When I was little,
我们找到一个男人
we found a man.
他看起来像被屠宰过
He looked like...like butchered.
村里的老女人一直画十字
The old women in the village crossed themselves...
祈祷着疯狂 奇怪的祷词
and whispered crazy things, such strange things.
魔鬼奉献
只有在最热的年份 才会发生这种事
Only in the hottest years this happens.
而今年也非常的热
And this year, it grows hot.
我们开始找到那些男人
We begin finding our men.
有些被剥了皮
We found them sometimes without their skin
有时更可怕
and sometimes much, much worse.
魔鬼奉献的意思是...
魔鬼把男人当作他的战利品
Means "the demon who makes trophies of man."
你下回要用什么作饵 芝士?
What you gonna try next, cheese?
达奇!
Hey, Dutch. Dutch!
他妈的!
Shit!
捉到你了! 捉到了!
I got you, you mother! I got you!
我来追你!
I'm coming!
麦克! 麦克!
Mac! Mac!
带他到直升机那里
Get Ramirez to the chopper.
好的
Right.
等一下 达奇
Hold it.
我去追麦克
I'm going after Mac.
不像你的一贯作风 狄龙
That's not your style, Dillon.
我从你这学了些坏习惯
I picked up bad habits from you.
你们快走吧!
Get your people the hell out.
你不可能赢的 狄龙
You can't win this, Dillon.
也许我可以报仇
Maybe I can get even.
狄龙!
Dillon.
你只要叫那直升机等我和麦克回来就好了
Just hold onto that damn chopper.
他伤得很重 少校
He's busted up pretty bad, Major.
我可以捱得住
I can make it. I can make it.
带走无线电 其它的都不要
Get the radio. Forget the rest.
好的!
Right!
走吧! 宾 我们走吧
Come on, Poncho.
老天
God!
高个子萨丽
"Long tall Sally"
她非常甜美
"she's built sweet!"
她什么都有
"She got everything that Uncle John need"
宝贝
"Oh, baby"
"Baby"
给我点快乐...
"I'm gonna have me some fun"
转过来
Turn around.
我在这里
Over here.
麦克
Mac?
嘘...
Shh.
麦克
Mac?
它在那里 在那些树上
Out there. Past them trees.
看得见吗?
You see it?
我看到你了
I see you.
我看到了
I see it.
是的 我看到了
Yeah...I see it.
现在我们可以杀了它
You know, we can get this thing, Mac.
你慢慢爬过去接近它
You work your way down there toward him.
我在上头逼近它后面 把它赶去你处
I'll get in back of him, flush him toward you.
当我赶那杂种时
When I flush the son of a bitch,
你就杀了它
you nail him.
我有个血海深仇要报
I got a score to settle.
我们都有仇要报
We've both got scores to settle.
赶快! 我们快走!
Come on! Quickly! Hurry up!
不要拿! 它没杀你是因为你没武装
Don't. Leave it. It didn't kill you because you weren't armed.
对它来说太没趣味!
No sport.
麦克! 麦克!
Mac. Mac.
好说
Anytime.
走吧!
Let's go.
比利!
Billy!
比利 我们走吧!
Billy, let's go!
给我武器 给我武器
Give me the weapon!
别拿!
No!
跑! 快走!
Run! Go!
去直升机那里
Get to the chopper!
他妈的
Oh, shit!
它看不见我!
He couldn't see me.
流血吧 杂种!
Bleed, bastard.
你真的丑得很!
You're one ugly motherfucker.
这主意真差
Bad idea.
过来 过来啊!
Come on. Come on!
快啊 来啊!
Do it! Do it!
来杀我 我在这里! 杀我啊!
Come on, Come on. Kill me! l'm here! Kill me!
来杀我! 我在这里
l'm here! kill me!
Come on, Kill me! l'm here!
来啊 现在来杀我
Come on, do it now! Kill me!
你到底是什么怪物
What the hell are you?